Now that we have all of our data stored
into a form data object, let's make that
post request. So we'll say axios.post
and we're going to go to our API
and
let's post
um the username and the username is
going to be form data.get
username
and then the password is going to be
form data.get get
password.
And then once we're done, let me zoom
out a little bit so you can see the full
line of code. Well, that's actually not
helpful. I'm just going to full screen
this for a little bit. So there is the
full line of code. We're making a post
request to that URL. We are sending over
that data and we're using the form data
object to gather the data.
Now, if we split it back onto two
screens and we open up db.json, JSON we
can say um hello and password of world
and if we hit submit we can see hello
and world came over with username and
password and that's how you can gather
form data and then use Axios to post